[{"answer": "This milk is bad", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Tuesday? I don't know. What's today", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Nothing that's open", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't know. You're the one who said it was bad", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well, let's see. What do you think is going to happen next, my friend", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No, you're not. You're going in there in two minutes and we are really going to nail this scene. I know it. I have no doubt about it. my friend..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, when did he ask you", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What, the guy can't even check into a hotel by himself", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Sounds kind of like an identity crisis", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "How'd you get into cinematography", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I never should have gone out last night. I hate jazz. God, I look terrible", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Don't bullshit me, my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Plus Chad is completely out of the light down there", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "It's your call, my friend. His acting or his face", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I lost it", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "That little light was set ten minutes ago", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Get me the A Team in here right away. my friend, my friend, and Mr. my friend.  Why didn't you tell me", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Oh, I am very worried about the time", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What is that supposed to mean", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I don't know what it means", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "What do you think it means?", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Oh yes you do, you know exactly what it means", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Oh yes you do, you know exactly what it means", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You don't understand me, my friend! You have no idea", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I've always admired you from afar", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You're right. How does despised sound", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "The fuck I do. I can't stand looking at you", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No, I think you have a lot more to say, my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Oh yeah", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Was I freaking out", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah. You were in the dream", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Actually, you were", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Scene thirt", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Oh, OK. Send somebody to my apartment to pick them u", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " What about the dolly", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Oh, I can't make it. I have to go see that plac", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Nothing. It's a little sensitive today", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": " Of course I can see", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Right, maybe you see him a little bit", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You see him", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I really don't like being spoken to like that, my friend", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I don't have an attitude", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "That's where the oil goes", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I'm tellin' you, my friend. That's where the oil goes", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I never said that", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I meant me! I feel fake! Everything I'm doing feels fake. I can't act. I should just do shower scenes in my friend movies for the rest of my life", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Tell me again", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Living-in-Oblivion.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "He doesn't have to be a dwarf", "qsentId": 50}]